[Revving car engine
then car drives off]
[Crickets chirping]
[Light TV buzzing sound]
[Thumping sound effect]
[Ominous music plays]
[Door opens]
[Sound of door closing]
[Footsteps approaching]
So what happened
to your wrist?
You've got the last interview
with the Meanest Man in
America, and that's
your first fucking question?
Suicide.
Who the fuck cares?
'cause if there's a hell
I'm going there anyhow.
Think about it.
Nobody in the great state of
South Carolina gonna believe
I'm dead till long
after they pull that switch.
You can believe,
think me a liar,
don't matter to me.
I'm famous now.
[Ominous music plays]
[Upbeat Christian music plays]
♪ They come together
from every place ♪
♪ Hearts open wide
before Your grace ♪
♪ They're all children
of God ♪
♪ Held by mercy,
held by love ♪
♪ Lead them, Lord,
into Your way ♪
♪ Guide their steps
both night and day ♪
♪ Your light still
rises over all ♪
♪ You never leave,
You never fail ♪
♪ Your faithfulness
will always prevail ♪
Hey, where you headed?
Jacksonville.
I'm headed in that direction.
Hop in.
It's your lucky day.
[song " At the Crossroads
of the Heart" plays]
Name's Lisa.
Nice to meet you, Lisa.
Friends call me Pee Wee.
Thanks, Pee Wee.
So, uh,
where you from?
Pennsylvania.
What're you doing
all the way down here?
Thought I'd see
the country a bit.
[Ominous sound effects]
In Jacksonville?
Miami, Key West.
Wherever the road takes me,
really.
Hmm.
Well, good for you.
Welcome to South Carolina.
♪ Two strangers met,
two worlds apart ♪
I hadn't seen anyone
for a while.
I was
starting to think I was gonna
have to camp out on the beach.
Yeah.
It is a dead time of year.
[Guitar solo]
Um, Pee Wee,
I think we missed the turn.
Oh, no
I'm taking a scenic shortcut.
I would hate
for you to miss it.
Sometimes
you only get one chance.
I done plenty of bad things.
[ominous music plays]
Robbed, hurt,
killed even.
Never really thought
about it much.
It just hit me when I saw her.
[crickets chirping]
Listen, I'd, uh, like a
little something for the lift.
I don't have much money.
No, just-
I was thinking maybe
something different, like
a hotel room in Savannah
for a couple of hours.
My treat.
Or maybe a little
something here.
[Giggles]
I
I don't pay for lifts.
Not like that.
What, you think it's funny?
That you'd let me fuck you?
I don't pay
for lifts, not that way.
Don't sass me, girl.
I'm not fucking around.
[Knife unsheathed]
You know what this is?
Please, please.
Put your hands on the dash.
Now!
[ominous sound effect]
Look at me.
Look at me!
I was gonna do whatever
I want with her.
She was mine.
That fucking laugh of hers.
[distorted giggles]
That look.
Disgust.
I did it.
Mm-hmm.
I did it right there.
[thumping sound]
[Choir music plays]
Funny, I went to church.
I did contractor work
for about every church in the
four-county area.
Well, I think we can do it.
I may have to talk to Uncle
Vernon about price,
but it's a good cause.
I just can't do it for free.
I was always looking for.
Something more.
Not work.
Where the missing won't be
missed, you know what I mean.
...at least not by
authorities anyhow.
Hey there.
Did you enjoy
the services today?
Yes, sir.
You like climbing trees?
Yes, I like climbing trees.
[Typewriter sound]
I like climbing trees too.
You're too big to climb trees.
You think that's funny, huh?
Tracey?
Oh, uh, sorry, I gotta go.
See you later.
I tried to keep my business
in Sumter
and my fun on the coast.
Coastal kills.
Worked at Donny's Garage
for a little bit.
Donny was an okay guy.
But sometimes,
Business got in the way.
Namely Clyde.
[Typewriter sound]
[Song "I Got So Much
Love to Give"]
♪ My dearest Love ♪
♪ I write tonight ♪
Thanks.
Make it quick.
I ain't renting space to two
businesses,
if you know what I mean.
Here. I need you to get hot
on this too.
Get him the hell outta here.
Be right on it.
That's what you said to me
last night, Pee Wee Gaskins.
[Donny whoops]
Clyde, you know you
don't want what
I got hanging here.
Pee Wee,
you know you love you some of
this chocolate now and then.
Ooh.
Is that true?
No.
She's just joking.
Oh, Pee Wee.
Now it's not just you who
likes a good old time with
old Clyde, now is it?
Clyde,
I like women.
White women.
Just like you.
I do love women.
And you and someone close
to you, know that.
All right, Clyde.
Leave the poor boy alone.
Go do what you gotta do.
Clyde was a drug-dealing pimp.
She liked men,
but she liked women more.
White women, black women,
it don't matter to her.
Hmm.
One thing for certain:
she was a pain in my ass.
You got the law's car
in there.
Is there anything
I should know?
No, it really is car trouble.
Wiring, which is my specialty.
You see the under-desk
wiring harness?
I really don't give a fuck,
Pee Wee.
I trust you.
I trust you too.
[Cars driving in the distance]
Hey Clyde,
just do me a favor.
Cut that shit talk
out about me.
I don't want anyone
getting the wrong idea.
[Song "A Young Man
On The Run"]
When was the last time
you saw Curtis?
I mean, I saw him yesterday,
and then he was like,
"I don't wanna see
you anymore,"
and then he locked
me out of the house.
[Song ends on the radio]
Hey sweetie.
[Radio] This song called
"A Young Man On The Run"
will surely become
a big hit!
Hi, Doreen.
Hi, Pee Wee.
How you been?
[Radio] I wanna talk about
networks of influence
[Radio] As you know, several
families here in Sumter
have quite some influence.
[Radio] Do you have some
specific people in mind?
[Radio] I'm talking about
the Butchers, the Robertsons,
even the Hatchers are friends
with the mayor
and can easily get favors.
[Muffled] Let's take the kids
to the river next week.
[Muffled] Mmm hmm, that'd
be nice.
[Radio] Hey, money talks,
right?
You damned
if I didn't forget something.
[Radio]
what do you want me to say?
That's the way the
world works.
See you later.
Pee Wee!
What?
Got some tools at the shop.
[Song plays on the radio]
You sure you wouldn't like
to stay?
What I like to do and what I
gotta do,
two different things.
See you later.
I swear he's always going off
in that stupid car.
Damn.
I was just a funny little
fella to everyone.
Everyone looked down on me.
All the big families, the
Robertsons, Butchers,
the Hatchers.
Shit.
So I decided to have
a little fun
especially
with them Robertsons.
Honey, you might want to close
that window over there.
Storm's coming in.
I'll get it in a second.
Turning in,
in case you're interested.
I'll be over in a jiff.
[Scream]
[Dramatic music plays]
There's someone out there.
I think it's Gaskins.
[Pee Wee's car engine starts]
There!
[Engine revving loudly]
He was there, Jim.
[Car sound fades away]
It was Gaskins,
I'm sure!
Oh God, Tracey.
[Police chatter on radio]
[Residential street
and cricket sounds]
Well, well.
Deputy Whitebread.
What can I do for you?
Hmm, what can I do to you?
It's Wilson, Clyde.
Deputy Wilson.
You all look the same.
Law enforcement, that is.
Sheriff got a complaint
saying some of your girls
have been straying up near Mr.
Streeter's on Main.
No idea what you mean.
I got no girls
other than my lovers.
If your lovers are going out
wearing clothes like that,
we're gonna
have some problems.
See that brunette?
Mm-hmm.
She's new, and the councilman
has come back
to tap her 4 times.
I think we have enough pull
to push into town a bit.
It's probably not worth the
hassle to mess with Sheriff
Hartry on this.
I appreciate it, sweetheart.
Anything else?
You've been hanging
around an ex-con.
Anything I should know about?
I just love little men, baby.
And I can make an exception
for you, Sergeant Sideburns.
Thanks, but I'll pass.
[Police Radio]
There's been a call from the
Robertson's residence
for disturbance.
Deputy Meyer is on his way.
[Car motor starts]
[Song "Promise Me You'll Wait"
plays]
Oh no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
This can't stay here.
What?
[car door closes]
Advertising one of my
businesses.
I'm an entrepreneur!
You don't even know what
the fuck that word means.
This weird shit
is just wearing me out.
Pee Wee, you got a reputation
and you're just...
What reputation?
You've done time for
attacking your cousin
with an axe.
I was young.
I know, but this doesn't help
when you're doing this
bizarre stuff.
I had some people come by
and try to tell me to
stop renting to you.
Influential people.
What'd you say?
Well, it don't matter.
You're a good mechanic, you
pay your rent,
you help me out.
They don't bring their cars
here, so I told them no.
What people?
It don't matter.
Just the way I am.
Where the hell you even get
something like this anyway?
Classified ad.
Some funeral home in Columbia.
They was having a bankruptcy
sale, so bought it and
figured I'd carry my shit
in it.
[car door opens]
I even fuck in it too.
Living or dead,
it don't matter to me.
Ah, damn Pee Wee.
[car door closes]
[dramatic music plays]
[Crickets and police
siren in background]
[Typewriter sound]
It's unlocked.
6, 7, 8, 9,
10.
[The engine starts]
Told ya, cuz, I used to
do this here all the time
back in New York.
Not like you slow-ass
motherfuckers down here.
Fucking-A, Henry!
What are you doing?
I'm too young,
you gotta drive.
I just didn't know
what to do.
He came in drunk, screaming
at me, and he threw a bottle
at my head
and it barely missed.
And then he just started
smacking me around...
I didn't know what to do.
And the he just
kept hitting me.
What the hell, Doreen?
You look like Shit.
Damn raccoon eye.
Curtis beat her.
Did you sass him?
I don't care much
for his type, but did you?
He didn't just hit
her, he beat her.
Well, he ain't coming
around here.
That's for damn sure.
She'll be fine.
I gotta go to Charleston
for a couple days to check on
the garage and Walter.
I think she'd feel better if
you stayed,
and I'd feel better.
You know what the hell I
got going on down there?
It's our money.
Walter's been acting
more quiet than usual.
Gotta see if it's just Walter
being Walter
or something's up.
Walter...
My business partner
in Charleston.
He was the not-so-strong,
silent dumb type.
But the man knew how to
chop a car, that's for sure.
[Song "A Young Man On
The Run" plays"
♪ He was raised on
rows of cotton ♪
♪ under long hot
summer skies ♪
♪ with a father
who kept hoping ♪
♪ he'd keep the farm alive ♪
[Typewriter sound]
Didn't expect you.
Hadn't heard
from you in a while, Walter.
How's tricks?
Dennis brought in a car.
Here.
Mmm.
Nice.
I paid him already.
How much?
Five on the dollar.
It's clean!
He didn't break the window.
Must be getting better.
I know he's your
brother-in-law, but
should we
make sure it runs first?
It runs just fine.
Got anything else for me?
One over there.
That's good to go.
All right.
so, how's Diane?
What the fuck that
supposed to mean?
Oh.
I guess she's still
with Avery.
[hood slams]
Listen, I'm gonna take this
for a spin before I head back.
Kinda like how Avery's
taking Diane for a spin.
Yeah, I could always get
a rise out of ol' Walter.
Start talking about his wife.
Visiting Walter was good
for one thing.
Coastal Hitchhikers.
They never found any of
your coastal kills, Pee Wee.
A lot
of people think you're lying.
You know, the swamp's a good
place to hide a body
'til a hurricane comes around
and sweeps up all your
bargaining chips.
And no one believes you.
That's fine by me.
[Song still plays]
[eerie sound effect]
Hey, sweet thing,
where you headin'?
Charleston.
I'm headin' there for work.
Get in.
Must be my lucky day.
You have no idea.
[Intense music plays]
[Jill sobbing]
Hush, hush.
[tools rattle]
Nobody going
to hear you out here.
[More sobbing]
I want to hear you beg.
[Jill screams louder
and louder]
[Squishing sound]
[More Squishing sounds]
Can you hear me?
Pee Wee.
Hey, Pee Wee.
Clyde's here.
All right.
Tell her I'll be right there.
Losing my patience, Pee Wee.
You know, uh, I didn't think
it was my place to mention,
but I saw your niece out
partying the other night.
So which one?
Janice.
And she was out
with your buddy out there.
What?
Seems like everybody in your
family's got something sweet
on Clyde.
Motherfucker.
Hello, Pee Wee.
Guess what I got?
I really don't give
a fuck, Clyde.
I've got a little Pee Wee
in my belly.
What?
What do you call
a little Pee Wee?
A wee Pee Wee?
Outside!
Now!
Come on.
What the hell
you think you're doing?
What'd I say?
You knocked me up.
You gotta stop with
this shit, Clyde.
Don't want
to be a daddy again?
I thought you'd want at least
one since your ex don't let
you see the kids.
Maybe I keep it.
Maybe I won't.
[dramatic sound effect]
Got something else for me
besides this little miracle?
Not yet, but, uh,
I might get something
stronger than usual.
Is that the big score you've
been promising, Pee Wee Daddy?
Mmm hmm.
Customers been digging
that shit.
Like my niece.
Business is business.
Black, white, brown,
they buy.
I sell.
Sell to anyone, Clyde.
Any color.
Keep that shit
away from my kin.
Maybe the good stuff
is on the house for me.
Maybe even a little bonus.
You know, for bein'
such a good salesman.
Why would I do that?
To make little
Pee Wee go away.
And to cool some of
that talk between me,
you,
and the wife.
[Kiss]
I hate to admit it, but-
she could really get under
my fucking skin.
[church music plays]
So I had to take care of that.
Reverend Parker.
I think our offer was fair.
It's very generous, but some
of the members want to bring
in some outside help.
But...
I'm sorry.
Wait for me there, son.
[Typewriter sound]
I tried
to run a real business.
With my uncle...
Vernon.
he weren't my real uncle.
He was just close with my mom.
Real close,
if you know what I mean.
So what is the problem?
[church organ plays]
I understand.
[Shake hands]
Can't win them all.
Why?
We good.
Fair, too.
Folks like the Hatchers,
the Robertsons,
they think
they're better than us.
They are the haves.
We are the have-nots.
So we take what we can get.
Yeah.
Take what we can get.
[dramatic music plays]
[eerie sound effects]
[knocking sound]
[sound of window opening]
I heard a noise outside.
Come!
[dramatic music plays]
Tracey, you stay
over there by your Momma.
Jim, what's going on?
You're scaring me.
[Suspense music builds up]
Jim, what's going on?
[sound of window shutting]
[more dramatic music]
Janie,
you've had so much.
[Typewriter sound]
I wanna leave.
We already left the party.
We're going home.
No, no, no, no.
I wanna leave Sumter.
[Cool folk music plays]
I'm bored.
You wanna leave Sumter?
And go where?
Anywhere.
This place is gonna kill me.
Okay, we are gonna get
you home
and then we can talk
about that.
No.
Come on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I love you.
Shut up.
No, you don't!
Uncle Pee Wee!
Hi!
What's going on?
Uh,
Janice ain't feeling too well.
I can see that, Patricia.
The question is why.
Well, she had a bit too
much to drink and a bit of
something else too.
You can get her in my car.
I'll take you back
to my place.
Both of you.
Sober up.
I don't want her momma
seeing her like this.
No!
Get up!
No.
Let's get!
You gotta open the door.
Hold up!
Push and push and then pull.
There we go.
Go!
No!
Gee!
[Door shuts]
Damn!
[Other door shuts]
What did she take?
I don't know,
but she had some pills.
From Clyde?
I think so, but I don't know.
Where were y'all at?
A party.
No one offered
to give you a ride?
I mean, I just took her
outside for a minute, get her
sobered up.
She kept going.
Hmm.
Well, we can go back
to my new place in Roper.
I don't want Norma
to see her.
Norma can't keep
a secret worth a shit.
It was weird.
She kept talking about
leaving, leaving Sumter,
and
she kept taking more and more.
What about you, Patricia?
I'm clean.
Bullshit.
[Engine revving]
[Crickets chirping]
[dramatic music plays]
Got her?
Nice and neat, now.
[Door shuts]
Got her?
[Girls giggle]
I don't like this.
Bathtub's over there.
Go get in it.
Take your clothes off,
it's going to get wet.
Take yours off too.
Got to help me.
Lift you in.
Wake up, Janie, wake up.
Patricia, no!
Here we go, here we go.
Can you just wake
up a little bit?
Help me out here.
I don't want to be here.
What are you doing, Pee Wee?
Helping you
take your shirt off.
Uncle Pee Wee...
Hey sweetheart.
Yes, Uncle Pee Wee.
Uncle Pee Wee's here,
it's going to be okay.
No, no, no.
Janice, help me a little bit,
a little bit.
I need you to come...
Get your hand off of me!
Get your hands off!
[Dramatic sound effect]
Uncle Pee Wee?
Yes, Uncle...
[Cracking bones]
Uncle Pee Wee,
what are you doing?
Sweetheart.
Patricia had an accident.
I'm gonna go take care
of her, okay?
Just stay here,
go back to sleep.
[dramatic sound effect]
You're a drug whore.
You turned my niece
into one, too.
Clyde's running you,
ain't she?
Ain't she?
Clyde's running you,
ain't she?
[Patricia hyperventilates]
[Sound of knife unsheathed]
You act like a whore, I'll
treat you like whore.
[Zipper being unzipped]
[Screams]
I'm sorry, Janice.
[rock music plays]
I never figured on all this.
The one thing I regret,
I let everything get to me.
I mean,
taking it out on my niece.
But the way she was acting,
I felt nothing but shame.
That made me angry.
[Rock music continues]
Let's go say hi to your momma.
Come on.
Carla.
[Typewriter sound]
What are you doing here
on a Sunday?
Or even at all?
Been a while, so I thought
it'd be good
to see some family.
You being here
ain't gonna work.
Hmm.
How's Janice?
Janice is fine.
Why do you ask?
Donny says she was hanging
around some questionable
people.
I hadn't heard anything
about that.
Just wanted to check in,
'cause we family.
I gotta get back
inside to lunch.
Nice to see you, too.
Ain't that right, Janice?
[eerie music plays]
I wanted to give you one last
chance to see your momma
in your house.
You know what?
I'm gonna make Clyde pay
for what she did to you.
Sweet child.
[Crickets chirping]
You wanted to see me,
Uncle Vernon?
[Christian song plays
on radio]
You've been dealing
to Janice.
I didn't.
What're you going
to do about it anyway.
You gonna hang me up like
when I was a kid?
You attacked that girl.
I should have done worse.
You did plenty.
Both of you to blame.
Wasn't like she was much
of a good momma anyway.
You leave your mama out
of this.
You care for her, Vernon?
Not like you're
fucking her anymore.
I am tired
of your crybaby shit.
Mama was a whore.
You got the hell
beat out of you.
Oh, you were neglected.
Shit, boy!
Take some responsibility!
She was a whore!
Come on.
She done the best
she could.
Most of your kinfolk
turned out fine.
Oh yeah?
Half brothers, half sisters
from a different dozen men.
She was a whore, Vernon.
Funny part is, ain't no
little baby Vernon's
running around.
What's wrong?
Can't get it up?
Maybe you're just
shooting blanks.
Watch it, Pee Wee.
I think the real
reason why you mad
is 'cause you don't want to
admit the only reason why she
was with you is 'cause
you put a roof over her head.
That's it.
I've had enough.
We're no longer
working together.
Yeah, that's fine.
I got my own shit going
on anyway.
Got a deal going on right now,
matter of fact.
Fucking Pee Wee.
Mm,
well, well.
Pee Wee Daddy.
Come in.
Got something for you, Clyde.
Grape drink?
And a swallowed grape drink?
You are trippin'.
You know I like the grape,
but that ain't gettin' me
to another world.
Oh, but it will.
It's got somethin'
special in there.
Like acid?
Mm-hmm.
You mean like LSD?
Something like that.
Don't go down too smooth,
though, it packs a punch.
[choking sounds]
Holy shit!
Goddamn!
[gasping sounds]
What you do?
What the hell you do?
[gasping sounds]
Oh yeah,
it's acid, Clyde.
Real
fucking acid, stupid whore.
No one's smarter than Pee Wee
motherfucking Gaskins.
I never thought anyone
was gonna miss Clyde.
Shit.
Boy was I wrong!
Kevin.
Sheriff.
I
wanted to talk to you about
some cases I think
may be connected.
I heard from her girls
that Clyde,
on the other side of
the tracks, she's been missing
for 2 days.
Martha Dixon, tall black
girl,
likes to dress like a man.
Yes, she's also been buying
drugs from Pee Wee Gaskins
and reselling, and his niece
and her friend are missing
as well.
What about the church?
You know Gaskins got every
single one of those members
up in a frenzy.
Now listen, Jim Robertson's
a good man, but his wife, you
know, she likes attention,
if you know what I'm saying.
No one's filed a report, so
that tells me
a lot right there.
And Clyde?
Let the detectives
do their job.
Henshaw didn't even
take a damn statement.
I'll talk to Henshaw, okay?
But look at it.
They're undesirables.
That's how I see it.
This feels off to me.
[dog barking]
[Knock on door]
[Car engine revving]
What the hell.
[Car door shuts]
Doreen.
Surprise.
What are you doing here?
Johnny dropped us off.
Why would he do that?
He thought you and Norma
might put me and Robin
up for a bit.
Where is Robin?
She's out back playing.
And, uh,
I'm gonna have another baby.
Well, yeah.
Not Johnny's?
No.
You gonna have another
nig-kid again?
Don't say that!
Well, it's true.
I'm a tolerant man, but
I do not abide by race mixing.
I know, but I was hoping you
and Norma could take us in.
Johnny don't want us.
Curtis just beats me.
You done business
with black folks?
Curtis and that Clyde woman-
What about my business?
What about Clyde?
[Atmospheric music]
Listen.
Norma's at her parents.
Why don't you come
out back and,
uh, play with Robin
for a little bit?
[Crickets chirping]
Not much of a pond.
Pretty from afar,
but up close,
ain't much to look at.
It's nice.
Cool in summer?
Mm-hmm.
Looky right here.
I think you can see
the sunset peeking out.
Yeah.
Doreen, look up there.
That's an egret.
See it?
Up in that tree right there.
Oh, yeah.
I'll go get your little one
so she don't run off.
She might want to see this.
[eerie sound effect]
[Scream]
[gurgling sound]
[gurgling stops]
[Crickets chirping]
[ominous music plays]
[thumping sound]
[rock music plays]
[Truck door slams shut]
[Rock song plays
on radio]
Howdy.
Yeah?
You rent a room
to a Martha Dixon?
Who wants to know?
I'd rather not show you
my badge, if I can help it.
No names.
Cash only.
Tall black woman
dresses in
men's clothes, goes by Clyde.
♪ My life is a dead end ♪
♪ stuck and slow ♪
♪ Like a broken sign
that says nowhere to go ♪
♪ My life is a dead end ♪
♪ words in my head ♪
[ominous music plays]
What the fuck?
They stole my sheets!
[Rock song plays
on radio]
Well, I'll be damned!
The boys actually did it.
[Truck doors shut]
Well, this is just
damn good work, Dennis.
Thanks, Pee Wee.
Just, uh, glad you gave
me the opportunity.
You're fine.
And, uh,...
The money?
Don't be afraid to ask
for what's yours, son.
Walter, get the man his money.
Wait here, Henry.
Hey, Superfly!
come over here.
Tell the truth.
Was it you
who did that work?
Dennis can't lift
like that.
I mean,
I don't like to brag.
Brag, son.
Come on, brag.
Plus, I like to know
who's doing what for me.
Well,
yeah.
You let him take the credit.
He's got the contacts.
Besides, he's my cousin or
half-brother,
some shit like that.
You ever think
about doing this on your own?
I mean, you got the talent
for it.
He's helped me since I got
down from New York, you know.
I don't know.
You gotta do what's best
for you, son, not him.
Come on, Henry.
Loyalty, Walter.
It's nice, but it
gets you in trouble.
[Traffic noises]
You won the star prize,
a brand new speedboat!
[Phone rings]
Oh, thank you.
I'll get it.
Hello?
You're some of the
stupidest...
Hello?
Greediest fuckers.
[ominous music plays]
Not him.
He's started back up again.
Damn it!
Yeah.
You wanted to see me, Sheriff?
I'm granting you your wish,
Kevin.
Which was?
I want you to open up
any cases with Gaskins ties.
I want you to harass people
he knows, badger him.
And even if you can't find
any solid links, let him know
we're investigating him.
Why the change in heart?
There was an obscene phone
call spree the other night.
Almost anybody with ties
to that church got them,
including the reverend.
So that's why I'm going
after him?
Phone calls?
Yeah, there's gonna be a mob
if this continues.
People are getting fidgety,
and someone's gonna end up
getting a little
trigger happy.
Don't care if Gaskins gets it.
But I can't have
any collateral damage in an
election year, so-
I'm on it.
Right away.
[upbeat music plays]
[ominous music playing]
[car door closes]
Now, what you explain next
is gonna determine
whether you live or die.
Put your hands up slowly.
Now turn around.
Name.
Will Hampton.
Why you keep crossing paths
with me?
I'm a fan of your work.
Stop blowing smoke
up my ass, boy.
Why you following me?
I got a business proposition
for you.
Make some real money.
I already make money.
How about $1,500?
And half a stash a man's
got up in his digs?
Tell me more.
My reputation started
spreading, so people started
hiring me to do things
for them.
I usually work alone,
But...
This one job,
I needed to bring Diane.
[Typewriter sound]
[Rock music plays]
[Knock knock knock]
Damn, Avery,
put you dick in your pants.
Hey, Pee Wee, what's up?
Need to speak with Diane.
Diane.
Put your jacket on,
and meet me outside.
Now anything you got to say
to Diane, you can -
Boy!
I thought I set
your ass straight.
Now I know you fuckin'
her in my garage.
And quite frankly,
I don't give a shit.
But if Walter finds out,
and there's bloodshed,
if he don't kill you first,
I will.
Got it?
Yeah, got it.
Come on, Diane.
Outside, now!
Close the damn door, Avery.
You know Walter's gonna kill
one or both of you, right?
Walter is too much of a pussy.
I could fuck Avery right in
front of him
and he wouldn't do a thing.
Yeah.
I got a proposition
for you.
[Rock music plays
on radio]
You, Pee Wee?
It ain't like that, Diane.
Don't get me wrong,
any other time,
mm-hmm,
I'd fuck you.
Ain't you a romantic.
How'd you like to make some
extra money off them gorgeous
titties of yours?
You can keep 'em covered, I
just need to use 'em as bait.
Go on.
I tell you,
you can't tell a
dickhead in there.
He ain't that bad.
Between him and Walter, you
must like 'em dumber
than shit.
But you can't say a thing.
Okay.
What is it?
[Rock song "So Tell Me"
plays]
[Crickets chirping]
♪ You told me once ♪
Thank God.
[Typewriter sound]
I need help.
My car broke down.
It's right over there.
[Rocking chair squeaking]
You wanna come inside?
Call your boyfriend?
Oh,
I don't have a boyfriend.
None right now.
Listen,
It's getting cold out here.
I can see that.
I'd love to make sure
it's running right.
I don't want to be stranded
out here at night.
♪ But I am losing you ♪
♪ So tell me what you hide ♪
It's over there?
I'd be so grateful.
All right.
This you car here?
Yes.
Nice car.
You ever, uh,
drive a sports car?
I'd love to.
With some real horsepower?
I wish.
Maybe one day.
All right.
Let's see.
[ominous music plays]
Well,
if you ever want to ride in
something
with some real horsepower-
I'd love that.
I'll take you out sometime.
Oh, really?
Shhhh.
Whoa.
Be real quiet.
Cuff him.
[handcuffs jangle]
What's going on here?
Where's your car keys and
where's your house keys at?
Keys in my pocket, man.
Go home.
Don't tell nobody about this.
[car door slams]
[ominous music plays]
Go put him on his knees
over there.
[Grunts]
[ominous music plays]
Got any last words for me?
Listen here,
you fucking leprechaun-
[Grunts]
Dumbest thing you can say
to a man with a knife.
[sounds of knife
breaking skin]
You paid me to kill him,
not to bury him.
Get to work.
What's the matter?
I just-
You ain't never seen
a man killed before?
Not like that.
Better get to work.
Start digging.
Or I'mma put you in
there with him.
[shoveling sounds]
[Rock music plays]
Haven't seen
you in a few days.
Need a word?
Been working on a project.
Not now.
I don't want you here no more.
What do you mean?
Look,
you do great work.
The problem is you attract
too much attention.
I ditched the hearse, but-
Yeah, it's not about that.
Look, when you were gone,
we had a visitor
asking questions at the shop,
a deputy.
He was asking all kinds
of questions.
Yeah, like
where you were,
what you were doing,
how long you missed,
just shit like that.
And I told you before,
I don't mind your work hours.
I don't mind your side jobs.
What I can't tolerate
is the police coming around,
snooping around, especially
when they're not dropping
their cars off,
which this one said
He ain't gonna be bringing
his cars by
if you're still here.
I see, Donny.
I was planning on making
Charleston a full-time thing
anyway, so-
Well, you got the talent
for it.
No hard feelings.
Nah.
[Accoustic guitar plays]
[gravel kicked up by the car]
Yeah,
well, tell me
what you need.
[Police car door
slams shut]
[dramatic music plays softly]
$500?
Paying that much?
[Knock knock knock]
I have to call you back.
Some joker outside
trying to talk to me.
Making some calls, Mr.
Gaskins.
Listen, uh, I'm gonna need
you to come in on some old
cases we have.
The ones with your niece,
friend, and Martha Dixon.
You know, we never did get
a statement from you.
Hmm.
My niece ran off.
Sheriff said so.
I don't know no Martha.
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
You don't know Martha.
Maybe Clyde rings a bell, hmm?
Yeah, we reopened that case.
New evidence has come up,
new witnesses, so we're
reexamining all the details.
You understand.
Here's my card.
You give me a call on
that sometime this week, we'll
meet up and question you, hmm?
Oh!
Almost forgot.
The hell is this?
A ticket.
You came up doing a 36.
It's a 35 zone.
You should know better.
Have a good night.
[Burning sound effect]
[Song "The Old Wardrobe"
plays]
[crickets chirping]
[Song continues on
the radio]
What're you doing here?
Looking for a screwdriver.
Listen, Norma,
I wanna talk
to you about something.
What?
Well, the garage in
Charleston's been doing good.
I mean, real good.
I don't think I gotta work
at Donny's no more.
OK?
So, I had someone offer me a
roofing job in Charleston,
and that means moving
to Charleston.
I'm not talking
a trailer neither.
I think we can get a house.
Are you kidding me?
No, a pretty nice one too.
We could even go see Walter,
hang out with our friend.
Well, that sounds nice,
except for the last part.
Well, I know, but ever since
Doreen went out west, like
her cousin Johnny said, you
ain't had many people over,
and it might be nice
to be around an old friend.
I'd like that.
Yeah?
All right, I'll go down to
the garage and start looking
for a new house.
Yeah?
Okay.
Now Charleston
was a fresh start.
I had no bad reputation there.
Made some friends too with,
uh,
some similar interests.
[typewriter sound]
[Rock song "This is
my American Dream"]
[Giggles]
[Indistinct whispers
and giggles]
[laughs]
♪ I don't need a promised
kingdom ♪
♪ Hanging somewhere
in the sky ♪
Dale!
Hey there, Pee Wee.
♪ Like a flag
I fly at night ♪
Oh, I see.
I see.
Again, Dale?
No, it's not like that.
Mm-hmm.
You ain't gotta lie to me.
You know I understand.
Yeah?
Yeah.
So young.
[ominous music plays]
So tender.
That's a sweet kiddy.
Mm-hmm.
You know, I think Micki
might want to go for a ride
with ol' Uncle Pee Wee.
You, uh,
you want to come along?
Yeah.
Let's go for a ride.
Hey, Micki!
[Rock song continues]
♪ Just don't let 'em
carve you ♪
♪ into someone ♪
♪ This is my American
dream, no halo, no cross ♪
Deputy.
Yes, Mr. Robertson.
I know you played a role in
running off Pee Wee,
but he's back.
You've seen him?
We were getting up past the
Roper Woods, about a mile or
so from here.
He was driving.
When was this?
Friday.
I don't think he noticed us.
He was too busy with those
guys in his car and a girl.
A little girl.
[girl sobbing]
That's my case.
Uh-huh.
Pee Wee Gaskins?
Do me a favor.
Get a real name for this guy.
And who called it in?
OK.
[ominous music plays]
[typewriter sound]
What's the
good word, Charlie?
You hear of a Pee Wee Gaskins?
No, don't think so.
Why, what's up?
A call came in from a
deputy in Florence
about our missing girl.
Our girl
from North Charleston?
That's the one.
And?
Said she was seen with this
older fellow driving around
up in Florence.
Time for us to head out
to Florence County.
Walter.
[ominous music plays]
Better have a good reason
for calling me out here.
I didn't want
to tell you this on the phone.
Diane wants to see you.
About what?
Don't know.
Just said business.
Hmm.
She at your place?
Where else would she be?
I don't know.
Out or something?
Here. Clean yourself up,
you look like shit.
[birds chirping]
[knocking on door]
[ominous music plays]
[TV on in background]
[door opening]
Hey, Pee Wee, come on in.
[door shuts]
Nice place.
Want to take a seat?
Diane, unless you gonna strip
and show me what God gave you,
I'll get going soon.
That girl,
the one at your party,
her picture's
in the newspaper.
Yeah.
She's missing.
I saw you and your molester
buddy talking to her.
So fucking what?
There were other people
at that party.
Said in the newspaper
that she disappeared
about a week later.
I told Avery.
He says it's a coincidence
and that the Pee Wee he knows
wouldn't want any cops banging
on his door.
Ain't nothing the cops
would be concerned about.
I hope not.
But if you did,
I'd want
to keep it between friends.
You know, like that job
we were in on together?
One where you paid me $100
to scare that guy and then
he went missing?
We can keep
it between you and me.
Avery ain't no friend of mine.
Well, maybe I can sit on it.
I wanted to go to the cops.
Anything to help
that poor girl.
But Avery thinks it's worth
$5,000.
$5,000? Oh, shit.
See what that jackass gets
for opening his mouth.
Says if you pay,
we'll be good.
He can't keep
a secret worth shit.
You, uh,
tell him about
that other thing.
No, I didn't.
And he won't talk about this?
He'll shut up for money.
Shit.
We can meet anywhere public,
out in the open.
All right.
you know my tenant house
over by Roper Woods?
Okay.
Yeah, meet me over there at
the crossroad by 7-Eleven,
right next to Sam's Bar.
Give me about
2 days.
I can do that.
Yeah.
Make sure you
bring shithead too.
He'll be there.
[door clicks open]
Sheriff Hartry?
Hi, this is Detective Bill
Ainsley with SLED down
in Charleston.
We're working a case over
here, and I was wondering if
you might know a guy by the
name of Donald Henry Gaskins.
I believe he's from up-
[indistinct Hartry
talk]
Oh,
uh-huh.
Okay, well, in that case,
I was wondering if we could
maybe meet with you and,
don't you have a Deputy
Wilson?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, perfect.
Yep. Alrighty, thank you.
You have a good one.
[crickets & neon noises]
[Song "Sometimes life
leans toward you" plays]
[pool balls clanking]
♪ I was counting all
the failures ♪
Hey, Pee Wee.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I told you to meet me over
by the crossroads at 7-Eleven.
Just finally wanted
to do some business.
Yeah.
Well, my money's
over at the tenant house.
Why don't you just
bring it here?
No, we'll follow you.
All right.
You know the way.
♪ Sometimes life leans
toward you ♪
Follow me.
♪ When your luck is
running thin ♪
Motherfuckers!
What the hell are you doing
going over there?
What?
The money's there.
In public, Avery!
Diane!
The money's there.
Come on!
[door opens]
[crickets chirping]
[car doors open and shut]
[ominous music plays]
The money's by the tree
over there.
You keep it in a tree?
Yes, a tree, Diane.
I don't trust Banks.
I don't want anyone tracing
anything back to me.
Makes sense.
How do we know you're
not trying to pull any shit?
For fuck's sake, Diane,
there's other places out here.
It's isolated.
What fuckers didn't meet me
when and where I told them to?
Fine, you stay out here in
the dark by yourself, alone,
and me and Avery
will go get the money.
[ominous music plays]
No, I'll go.
[Suspenseful music]
Oh, fuck.
Come here.
Shh. Sit quiet.
Come on!
Now you know I'm gonna have
to kill him for putting those
ideas in your head.
I'm gonna let you live
for Walter's sake.
But you gotta stay real
quiet and get on
your knees over here.
[sound of knife cutting
and grunts]
[gory sounds]
I said not one word!
[dripping blood sound]
You had to know
I'd done this before.
So why?
Why?
He wanted to do it!
You know he
wanted more.
Hmm?
I know, I just thought-
You thought you had old
Pee Wee by the balls,
didn't you?
Greediest motherfuckers.
[BANG! BANG! BANG!
BANG!]
[whimpering sound]
[BANG!]
[Sound of body fall]
Waste of good titties.
[birds chirping]
Clean here.
[country music plays]
Good work, boy.
What'd I tell you?
What'd I tell you, Walter?
He's a superstar.
Superstar.
Come here, son.
Mmm.
Dale, how you doing?
Good to see you.
Under 10 seconds?
That's what I'm talking about.
Uh-huh.
Damn good work.
The hell's wrong
with you, boy?
Where's my sister Pee Wee?
How the hell should I know?
Probably fucking Avery
or something.
See, I know what
she was gonna do to you.
I know what you did to her.
Boy,
you had too much to drink.
You need to shut up now.
Yeah, I'm gonna fuck you-
[fist hitting face]
[body blow]
You want something too?
You need to part ways
from him.
'cause we done.
He better watch his ass,
and if you going to stay
with him,
you better watch yours too.
Come on, Walter.
Walter.
What'd you find out?
He's been talking.
To the police?
No, he wouldn't.
He wasn't all that close
to Diane.
I think he just wants money.
And he wants to
come back?
That's what he says.
Hmm.
But-
Sounds like bullshit.
Mm-hmm.
I was thinking the same thing.
You know he's gonna try to do
something with the garage,
right?
We can't let that happen.
Walter,
I'm gonna need to know
how far you willing to go.
[ominous music plays]
[crickets chirping]
[door opens]
What a surprise,
you brought Henry.
Yeah,
the kid wanted to tag along.
Look, I know you're angry,
but you do good work, so
I got you something, something
nice, something foreign.
Thanks, Pee Wee.
Listen,
I'm sorry, man.
I just had a little too much
to drink and made a fool out
of myself, and I,
I'm sorry.
Listen, it's in
that grove over there,
far away from any houses.
Walter, Why don't you go
make Henry a sandwich?
Me and Dennis got
some business to talk about.
Listen,
I want you to know I didn't do
anything to your sister.
It's right over here.
Over there?
Yeah, over by that tree.
Anything special
about this place?
I figure we could, uh, throw
some chains on
that tree branch.
Maybe lift some engines.
I think you might be right.
You know, you gotta be crazy
to wear a jacket in South
Carolina this time of year.
[ominous music plays]
[gun clicks]
You know what?
I think I got just the thing
for that, -
[muffled gun shot]
[squishing sound]
[Sound of body fall]
Car's out here!
Car's out here?
Yeah, some girl I know
called it isolated.
If it means dark and
creepy as fuck,
She's right!
Yeah.
What the-
[gun shot]
Told you not to
run with him.
[gun shots]
You okay with this?
All right,
Now we get them in the grave.
This ain't the first
time you done this,
is it?
That's correct.
[crickets chirping]
Anyone else out here?
Johnny?
I ain't seen him in a while.
Not here, but-
Yeah.
[banjo music plays]
He ain't coming back neither.
Be scary as shit if he did.
Avery?
Mm-hmm.
I reckon Diane.
Sure you wanna know?
She was going to
blackmail me.
Her and Avery.
Walter, I didn't want to.
I really didn't,
but-
Avery was an asshole.
Yeah.
He were at that.
Anyone else?
Yeah, some you know.
Some you don't know.
You want to give me a hand
with this here?
[guitar solo]
[music now plays
on radio]
[car door opens]
[car doors close]
[birds chirping]
[knocking sound]
Gaskins, open up!
We've got a warrant!
[knocking sound]
Gaskins!
[dramatic sound effects]
[banjo music on radio]
[dramatic music plays]
Sheriff.
[car driving off in
background]
Son of a bitch.
Might be the Charleston girl.
And I bet them shoes
ain't his either.
[dramatic music]
Norma?
Hey, it's Walter.
Yes, listen,
have you seen Pee Wee?
You know where he's at?
I really need to talk to him.
Okay.
[phone hang up]
[dialing sound]
Terry,
it's Walter.
You know where Pee Wee's at?
Yeah.
They talked to him too.
I think something's
wrong.
He just
up and disappeared.
[hanging up phone]
[eerie sound effects]
Diane...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Dennis Bell?
And Henry King?
How many days?
Really?
Wow.
Okay.
What do we got?
So it turns out Dennis Bell
and Henry King haven't been
seen for days.
So that's 2 people who used
to hang around his garage,
neighbor girl, these 4 other
people, and a little girl
outside Sumter.
If he has a problem
with someone, they disappear.
Seems like it.
[phone ringing]
Detective Ainsley.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Yeah, he's with me.
Uh, McNeil?
Now?
We'll be right down.
Let's go.
Walter McNeil wants to talk.
I think he's found religion.
Bet he has.
[sound of neon light]
So I helped him
bury Dennis and Henry
at his place in Roper Woods.
And he starts talking
about how he killed Johnny.
Then he says what he done
with Avery and Diane,
my wife and
her boyfriend.
There's some joke on me.
[ominous music plays]
Then he starts talking
about his private graveyard.
Hitchhikers, mob hits,
the taste of human flesh.
Says he had a hearse
and hauled body parts in it.
You need any more?
Yeah.
Go on.
[engine cuts off]
[door opens]
[car wooshes by]
[car door closes]
[dialing sound]
Norma?
Yeah, it's me, Pee Wee.
Listen, baby, I
might have to go away
for a while.
Yeah, I gotta get out of town
before these lawmen
come get me.
Mm-hmm.
Getting hot and heavy.
[car engine outside]
Oh, shit.
Speak of the devil.
Out of the phone booth!
Call you back, baby.
On the ground,
Now!
Out of the phone booth,
get on the ground, now!
Come on, come on!
Easy, easy.
Hands behind your back.
Donald Henry Gaskins, you're
under arrest for contributing
to the delinquency of a minor.
You have the right
to remain silent.
[car door shuts]
[dramatic music plays]
Come on, Walter.
[shovel sounds]
Take us to them bodies.
[flies buzzing]
Uhh.
That's Henry.
My God, how do you know?
Recognize the shirt.
Must be that burial ground
he was telling you about.
Oh God!
[vomiting sound]
[coughing sound]
[dramatic music intensifies]
[vomiting sound]
[flies buzzing]
I take it that's Diane.
[thumping sound]
Alright, Donald.
Who else we got
buried out there?
Well,
who else you got right now?
I got, let's see, got Mr.
Dennis Bell.
[gun shot]
Mr. King.
[gun shots]
How about Avery Hamilton?
[stabbing and grunts]
Diane McNeil.
Mm-hmm.
[gun shot]
Doreen Daniels and her baby,
[scream]
not counting her unborn child.
That makes 6, sort of, if you
count
that unborn colored child.
[omimous music starts]
Yeah,
that should be good enough
to keep you boys
plenty busy.
But why?
Why all that?
Business.
Mostly,
except for, uh, Doreen there.
Yeah,
ain't nowhere as interesting
as my coastal kills
or them
hits I did for the mob.
Well, you flatter yourself.
Sounds like you proud
of what you did.
Mm-hmm.
Fucking disgusting.
There's a special place
in hell for guys like you.
Oh, yeah?
I feel bad for guys like you.
You don't know what
real freedom is.
You don't know how to take
power into your own hands.
You make me sick.
Better than being the one
in the cuffs.
Once you decide
to kill anybody,
Anytime, anywhere,
in any way you want.
Once you get to that point,
you set yourself free.
[dramatic music plays]
Funny.
I escaped the death penalty
for doing all that.
But I kill some nigga on
death row and they give me
the electric chair?
Yeah.
I made sure no one
won't forget me.
[door opens]
Pee Wee, it's time.
All right, let's go.
This is Donald Pee Wee
Gaskins saying goodbye
for now.
[recorder button clicks]
[music stops]
[song "Promise me you'll Wait"
plays]
♪ The train ♪
♪ is waiting ♪
♪ on the track ♪
♪ My bag is heavy ♪
♪ on my back ♪
♪ The army calls ♪
♪ I have to go ♪
♪ But I love you, honey ♪
♪ I hope you know ♪
♪ Oh darling, please wait
for me ♪
♪ Across the land,
across the sea ♪
♪ My heart is yours ♪
♪ My love is true ♪
♪ I promise I come ♪
♪ home to you ♪
♪ Oh baby,
keep your faith in me ♪
♪ No matter where this road
may be ♪
♪ my arms will hold you ♪
♪ I swear I'm coming back
to you ♪
♪ They called my name ♪
♪ They called ♪
♪ it loud ♪
♪ But leaving you ♪
♪ breaks my heart, now ♪
♪ I feel your tears
falling softly ♪
♪ on my face ♪
♪ Oh, I wish I could stay,
stay in this place ♪
♪ Oh, darling, please wait
for me ♪
♪ across the land,
across the sea ♪
♪ My heart is yours,
my love is true ♪
♪ I promise I come
home to you ♪
♪ Oh baby,
keep your faith in me ♪
♪ No matter where this road
may be ♪
♪ my arms will hold you ♪
♪ I swear I'm coming
back to you ♪